

## **Details**

**5** 778-239-3874

m rodrielnt@gmail.com

Port Coquitlam, Canada

## **Skills**

UX/UI Design

Web development

**IOS** Development

Android Development

Agile Development

Test Driven Development

Clean Architecture

**DDD** Domain Driven Design

Bloc Pattern

#### Languages

Dart

Js JavaScript

Ts Typescript

Python

Tython

5 HTML

₹ CSS

☆ GraphQL

#### Frameworks/Libraries

Flutter

Angular

🕓 jQuery

**&** GetX

Svelte

# Rodrick Vyizigiro

Flutter Developer

### **Profile**

I am a front-end software developer with 4 years of experience in Flutter and User Experience Design. I have 2+ years of hands-on Flutter development creating adaptable web, mobile, and desktop applications. I have worked with back-end systems like Firebase, Heroku, Cloud Run, Identity Platform, Cloud Storage and other GCP APIs.

# **Employment History**

### Flutter Developer, Luminucx

Jun 2019 − Sep 2022 Port coquitlam

Took an active role in the start-up, launching the first MVP product, and worked actively with the system designer to create a flutter framework, packages and internal tools.

- Pair programmed a successful multi-language web app in Flutter.
- Timely delivered a design and prototype of an app in Figma.
- Created complex widgets for use cases following Clean Architecture.
- Conducted performance testing and optimization using Dart DevTools.
- Worked on back-end authentication and database features with GCP and Firebase.
- Created HTTP servers in dart using Cloud Functions.
- Designed and pair programmed a framework that enforced Clean Architecture in apps.
- Created a Flutter theme generator application with a companion Dart package.
- Conducted competitor audits and usability studies.

### Front-End Developer Contract, Dr Mura Health

Designed and created a course website for a lifestyle intervention medical practice that served online users.

- Effectively collaborated with the client to meet their needs.
- Designed & prototype their website using AdobeXD.
- Used Angular and Typescript with Firebase storage, authentication and database services.
- Built a CMS that served their content management needs.
- Successfully maintained the site serving users.

#### Volunteered To Create Remote Area Community Hotspots, TIES

Created RACHEL units with Raspberry-Pi to serve students in third-world countries with access to educational websites & resources in an offline format.

### Volunteer As Graphics Designer, Westminster SDA Church

Aug 2020 − Present 

New Westminster

I collaborate with a team to design slides used to show transitions, and announcements when streaming a worship service.

# 

# Hobbies

Heroku

Hiking, cooking, publicspeaking, graphic design, cycling & reading.

# Education

### Ebus Academy, High School Diploma

Jun 2023 Port Coquitlam

# Courses

### 2021 Flutter Development Bootcamp, Udemy

Jun 2022 - Jul 2022

# Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design, Coursera

Jul 2022 — Aug 2022

# Google UX Design Certificate, Google

May 2022 - Present

# **Values**

I am a **pragmatic** programmer, with a focus on **quality**, a passion for **design** and a taste for **clean code**.

# References

References available upon request